myliker.com 2014-03-06

# Privacy Policy - Facebook Auto Liker - MyLiker

Myliker.com is a Like Exchange website where we need access token to exchange likes on Facebook Automatically. So our site use your Facebook Access token for Like Exchange. We use your Access Token only for likes, comment and followers exchange. 

Myliker.com is trust and Safe Facebook Auto liker. We never use your access token for our personal use because myliker is like exachange website to increase likes on Facebook status, photo and Page.

##  **Our Terms and Conditions**  

Please Never Share your Access Token to other peoples and websites.

We will Never Responsible for any problem with your Facebook Account.

We will Never Responsible if Facebook Account suspended while using myliker

Never Share your Access Token to other people and other website.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. 

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Myliker has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: Myliker.com 

RC-31, Sangam Park, Khora Colony,   
Ghaziabad pin code: 201010  
blogstoc@gmail.com This document was last updated on January 21, 2014
